Beto提到我们应该为不同分辨率的手机提供多种位图图标
Beto mentioned that we should provide bitmaps at different resolutions.
在我们的应用程序中  Nexus S使用的48dpi的图标
In our app, the 48dp icon on the Nexus S looks to be about the same size
看起来与Nexus 4和Nexus 5使用的图标尺寸一样大
as on the Nexus 4, and on the Nexus 5.
但是实际上  用像素来计算的话
However, in reality, this asset that's being displayed,
这个图标显示的尺寸要大得多
is actually a lot bigger in terms of pixels compared to this one.
为了确认这一点  我们可以查看应用程序的资源文件夹
To confirm, we can check out the app resource folders.
在drawable文件夹中  我们看到应用程序为mdpi的设备提供了一个48×48像素的启动图标
In the drawable folders, we see that our app has a 48 x 48 pixel launcher icon
它被放在drawable-mdpi文件夹中
for mdpi devices located in the drawable mdpi folder.
对已分辨率更高的设备  为了达到同样的效果
To make an equivalent icon, for the higher density devices,
我们需要这个图标变得更大
we need to make that icon progressively larger.
为了弄清这些图片究竟要多大
To know exactly how big to make these images
以及如何将它们转换为像素更高的图片
and what the dp pixel conversion should be,
我们使用mdpi分辨率屏幕的设备作为基准
we use an mdpi device as the baseline.
这里一个dp相当于一个像素
This is where one dp equals one pixel.
然而在HDPI分辨率的设备上 一个dp等于1.5个像素
Then on the HDPI device, one dp equals 1.5 pixels.
以此类推  对于XXHDPI分辨率的设备
And then it increases from there, all the way to an XXHDPI device,
一个dp等于4个像素
where one dp equals four pixels.
更多的换算  可以查看下面的链接
For more info on the conversions, see the link below.
遵循这些规则  我们可以在drawable文件夹中
Following those rules, these are the sizes of the launcher icon
查看不同尺寸大小的启动图标
in our drawable folders.
MDPI分辨率的屏幕使用的图标像素是48×48
The MDPI one is 48 pixels x 48 pixels.
HDPI的是这个的1.5倍
The one for HDPI is 1.5 times the size of this one.
在XHDPI的设备上  图标像素是mdpi的2倍
For an XHDPI device, the icon is two times the size of the MDPI one,
对于XXHDPI分辨率的设备  图标像素是这个的3倍大小
And for an XXHDPI device, the icon is three times the size of this one.